[{"question": " wow! that ripped! that ripped real nice!", "answer": " how many times do i have to tell you! ya, turn and sliiiide! y'know, turn and slide.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " you don\u0092t turn and slide, you throw it out! i\u0092m tired of having to get a tetanus shot every time i get dressed!", "answer": " look, we\u0092re not throwing it out! i built this thing with my own hands!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " all right, how about we, how \u0091bout we sell it.", "answer": " all right. but, you\u0092re gonna have to tell them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  hey monica, it\u0092s chip.", "answer": " yesss!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " who\u0092s chip?", "answer": " shhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  good runnin\u0092 into you at the bank today, so ah, here\u0092s my number, 555-9323. give me a call. later.", "answer": " chip, is chip matthews.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " the guy who took rachel to the prom? why is he calling you?", "answer": " \u0091cause i ran into him at the bank, he is still soo cute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " monica, you\u0092re so lucky! he\u0092s like the most popular guy in school!!", "answer": " i know!!   chip? hi! it\u0092s monica.  \u0091kay.  \u0091kay.  okay.  okay, good-bye.  oh my god, we just had the best conversation!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  i was just leaving.", "answer": " good! \u0091cause i\u0092ve got a product report to read, it\u0092s like eight pages, i hope i don\u0092t fall asleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " why? did you write it?", "answer": "  wow! look at that, chip matthews called. i wonder what he wants?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " well ah, actually...", "answer": "  i bet he sensed that i was ready to have sex with another guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, umm, why don\u0092t you give him a call?", "answer": " okay.  are you sure you wanna hear this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh, i\u0092m sure.", "answer": "  chip! hi, it\u0092s rachel.  rachel green. yeah, umm, you left me a message.  yes you did, my roommate wrote it down.  monica geller.  ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": "  ...dumb, drunken, bitch!!!   thank you, thanks.", "answer": "  hey, here\u0092s a question; where did you guys get the finest oak east of the mississippi?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " uh-huh, first you tell us where you got the prettiest lace in all the land.", "answer": " i\u0092m reading your ad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " looks good, uh?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh my god, you guys are selling the entertainment center?", "answer": " why? i love that thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " you want it? phoebe and rachel: oh no.", "answer": " ahh, gepeto, $5,000 dollars? are you insane?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey, the ad alone cost 300 bucks!", "answer": " all right look, i\u0092m changing it to 50 bucks, or your best offer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " what kind of profit is that?! and you call yourself an accountant.", "answer": "  nooo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh. what do you do?", "answer": " i can\u0092t believe you don\u0092t know what i do for a living!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " yeah, i actually don\u0092t know...", "answer": " good, so do i", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh my god! no! shoo! kitty! no! no-no-no! shoo! come on, you!  come on. crazy.  oh my god.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " nothing. nothing.", "answer": " what? what\u0092s wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " i just, i just have this really strong feeling that this cat is my mother.", "answer": " you mean the mom you met in montauk. she was a cat?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " no, no-no, she was a human lady. this is the spirit of my mom lily, the one who killed herself.", "answer": " are you sure she\u0092s in the cat, or have you been taking your grandma\u0092s glycoma medicine again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " no dr. skeptismo! i\u0092m sure. first of all, okay, there\u0092s the feeling.  okay, and for another, how about the fact that she went into my guitar case which is lined with orange felt.  my mother\u0092s favourite fish is orange roughy...  cats....like....fish!   hi, mommy.  oh, i haven\u0092t seen this smile in 17 years!", "answer": "  dude, phoebe\u0092s mom has got a huge peni...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " umm, when were you gonna tell me that you\u0092re going out with chip matthews?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " now? is it okay if i go out with chip matthews?", "answer": " nooo! it\u0092s not okay! i can\u0092t believe you would want to after what he did to me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " what, that little thing at the prom?", "answer": " monica! i couldn\u0092t find him for two hours! he was having sex with amy welch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " come on, that was back in high school! how could that still bother you?", "answer": " i mean why, of all people would you want to go out with chip?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " look, you and i went to different high schools...", "answer": " okay, that doesn\u0092t help me, because we went to the same high school.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " you went to one where you were popular, and you got to ride off chip\u0092s motorcycle, and wear his letterman jacket. i went to one where i wore a band uniform they had to have specially made.", "answer": "  they had to have that specially made?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " it was a project for one of the home ec classes.", "answer": "  oh my god, they told us that was for the mascot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " back then, i thought that i would never, ever get the chance to go out with a chip matthews, and now he\u0092s-he\u0092s called me up and asked me out. and the fat girl inside of me really wants to go. i-i owe her this. i never let her eat.", "answer": " oh, you go out with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh, really?!", "answer": " yeah. just, if it\u0092s possible, could you leave him somewhere and go have sex with another guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " so you guys having any luck getting rid of the entertainment center?", "answer": " well, there were a couple of calls last night, but ah, i don\u0092t think any of them are gonna work out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yes, joey has a very careful screening process. apparently, not everyone is qualified to own wood and nails.", "answer": "  stop it! stop it! she keeps squirming, trying to get away! just like when she was alive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " so pheebs, how long is your mom gonna be with us?", "answer": " well, i\u0092m not sure. i mean, i guess until she y'know, gets used to the fact that there\u0092s y'know, a new mom. y'know, i think she\u0092s worried that y'know, she\u0092s gonna, she\u0092s gonna be replaced.  well, that\u0092s not gonna happen is it? noo.  okay, i have to return a call in the other room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " why can\u0092t you use the phone in here?", "answer": " well, i\u0092m returning a call from a certain mom at the b-e-a-c-h. i just spelled the wrong word.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " so, guys, am i crazy, or does phoebe\u0092s mom remind anyone of a cat?", "answer": " ross, don\u0092t start.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " come on, you-you can\u0092t tell me you actually believe that-that there\u0092s a woman inside that cat!", "answer": " i believe it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " no you don\u0092t.", "answer": " yes, i do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " no you do--y'know what, you\u0092re not gonna suck me into this.", "answer": " oh sure i am, because you always have to be right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " wow! that\u0092s ah, that\u0092s pretty nice!", "answer": " pretty nice?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " you\u0092ll have to pardon my roommate, he wanted to marry this.", "answer": " we don\u0092t have 50 bucks, but would you be willing to trade for it? we\u0092ve got a canoe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " y'know, i, i really don\u0092t think we need a canoe.", "answer": " you gotta take the canoe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " all right, just, just take the entertainment center, and then when you get home, throw the canoe away!", "answer": " we\u0092re not throwing it away! i built that canoe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  you guys, you\u0092re never gonna believe what i just found tacked up on a telephone pole!  look kinda familiar?", "answer": "  apparently phoebe\u0092s mother also goes by the name julio.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " you guys, there\u0092s a little girl in soho looking for this cat. i mean, you know what that means?!", "answer": "  yeah-eah! 200 dollar reward, split five ways!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " do we have to tell her?", "answer": " yes, we have to tell her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " oh, but it\u0092s made her so happy.", "answer": "  little girl misses her cat.  crazy lady thinks her mother is in a cat.  okay, y'know what, i have to go have dinner with my son, can i trust that when you see phoebe, you will tell her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": "  yeah.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i hate when ross is right!", "answer": " he is right, isn\u0092t he?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " y'know what, i think this might be one of the times he\u0092s wrong.", "answer": " you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " uh, pheebs, about your mom...", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  how\u0092s that going?", "answer": " so great. oh, we took a nap today and my mom fell asleep on my tummy and purred.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " pheebs...", "answer": " i just feel so, uhh.....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " all right!!", "answer": " i\u0092m coming already!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hello, chip.", "answer": " hey, rach! how ya doin\u0092?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i\u0092m great! i\u0092m great. i\u0092ve got a great job at bloomingdale\u0092s, have wonderful friends, and eventhough i\u0092m not seeing anyone right now, i\u0092ve never felt better about myself.", "answer": " so ah, monica ready yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " she\u0092ll be out in a second. so, chip, how\u0092s umm, amy welch?", "answer": " amy welch? wow! i haven\u0092t seen her since... so, monica about ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " this is the unit for you my friend. sturdy construction, tons of storage compartments, some big enough to fit a grown man.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh yeah! i got in there myself once. my roommate bet me five bucks that i couldn\u0092t, and then he stuck a board through the handles that locked me in. yeah. it was funny \u0091til i started feeling like i was in a coffin.", "answer": " no, you, you can\u0092t fit in that thing. that\u0092s not deep enough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh yeah?  if i can\u0092t, i\u0092ll knock five bucks off the price off the unit.", "answer": " all right, you have yourself a deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " here, we are.", "answer": " oh my god! you still have the chipper!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " the what?", "answer": " that\u0092s what we used to call your ah, your motorcycle in high school. y'know how a motorcycle is a chopper, and you\u0092re chip. nevermind.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " wow! a lipper from chipper.", "answer": " so you still in touch with anyone from high school?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " umm. well, there\u0092s rachel, and umm, i think that\u0092s it. how bout you?", "answer": " oh yeah, i still hang with simmons and zana, y'know. i see spindler a lot. devane, kelly, and i run into goldie from time to time. steve brown, zuchoff, mcgwire, j.t., breadsly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " is that all?", "answer": " ehh, y'know after high school, you just kinda lose touch. oh yeah! i ran into richard dorfman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " ohh, how is he?", "answer": " not so good, simmons and i gave him a wedgie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " isn\u0092t he an architect now?", "answer": " yeah, they still wear underwear.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " oh my god!!!", "answer": "  what?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " are you all right?!", "answer": " yeah...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": "  what happened?!!", "answer": "  awww, man! he promised he wouldn\u0092t take the chairs!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " what the hell happened?!! how were you locked in?!! and where the hell is all of our stuff?!!", "answer": " well, this guy came by to look at the unit and-and he said he didn\u0092t think big enough to fit a grown man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " so--you got in voluntarily?!", "answer": " i was tryin\u0092 to make a sale!! oh, man, if i ever run into that guy again, do you know what i\u0092m gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " look, not that i enjoy talking about people who i went to high school with, \u0091cause i do, but umm, maybe we could talk about something else? like you, i don\u0092t even know where you work?", "answer": " you know where i work!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i do?", "answer": " the movie theatre, you used to come in all the time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " you still work at the multiplex?", "answer": " oh, like i\u0092d give up that job! free popcorn and candy, anytime i want. i can get you free posters for your room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " thanks, i\u0092m set. do you still live with your parents?", "answer": " oh yeah, but i can stay out as late as i want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " wow! they really got you guys. your t.v. the chairs.", "answer": " oh yeah, your microwave. the stereo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  aww, man, he took the five of spades!! oh, no-no-no, here it is!", "answer": "  oh my god! what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh, umm, joey was born, and then 28 years later, i was robbed!!", "answer": "  so, how was your date?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " well, y'know how i always wanted to go out with chip matthews in high school?", "answer": " um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " well, tonight, i actually went out with chip matthews in high school.", "answer": " oh honey, i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " no, it\u0092s okay, not only did i get to go out with chip matthews, i got to dump chip matthews.", "answer": " ohh! that\u0092s so great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " i know!", "answer": "  hey! so ah, what did the insurance company say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh, they said uh, \u0093you don\u0092t have insurance here, so stop calling us.\u0094", "answer": "  you didn\u0092t tell her?!  okay, fine! pheebs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " yeah?  hi!", "answer": " hi! listen uhh, this cat belongs to a little girl. there are flyers all over the place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " hey, we can take her back with you if you want.", "answer": " ohh. um-hmm. but y'know, she choose to find me. i mean, i have to respect her decision. right? chandler, monica, joey, and rachel: that\u0092s a good call. right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " no! no! look--hey, enough is enough! look, i am sorry that you feel guilty or whatever about spending time with your new mom, but this is not your old mom. this is a cat! okay, julio the cat! not mom! cat!", "answer": "  ross, how many parents have you lost?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " none.", "answer": " okay, then you don\u0092t know what it feels like when one of them comes back. do you? i believe this is my mother. even if i\u0092m wrong, who cares? just be a friend. okay? be supportive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know what to say.", "answer": " you could.... say you\u0092re sorry to her mom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " i think she would like that.", "answer": "  come here, here, come here, come here,  mrs. buffay. sorry, about what i said, umm, it was, it was insensitive of me to say that you were just a cat. when clearly you are also the reincarnated spirit, of my friend\u0092s mother.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " thank you. we both forgive you.", "answer": " so honey, what are you gonna do about the little girl?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah, okay, listen, umm, mom, i hope you know you still mean a lot to me. and you\u0092re welcome to come back anytime.", "answer": " pheebs, if she could come back as a couch, we\u0092d really appreciate it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " come on, mom, i\u0092ll take you home.", "answer": " i\u0092ll go with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " oh! y'know, i\u0092ve got an extra futon.", "answer": " dude, you don\u0092t have to brag! we got nothing here!! closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}]